Bobby Hilton here from the shark stream
at the international 2024 with the great
Neils Fen how you doing Neils good good
relieved that was a big match right
there by feder you want to talk us to
that tell us a little bit about how the
match went yeah I mean uh you know feder
is one of the hottest guys on the tour
of course he won the World Championships
and the US Open uh played him in the
semis at the open so I kind of wanted to
get back at him you know from the inside
but it's tough enough and uh his break
wasn't really working in the beginning I
was breaking pretty good all match um
was Taking My Chances he made a couple
errors so all of a sudden I'm up like
84 um and then you could see like the
energy start shifting in the room there
like more people coming in you know got
a little tense and I'm up like
94 uh and then I make a just a push out
error he runs out he breaks runs out you
know 96 then I make a blunder I get a
really good a good open rack and I
missed the three I just got nervous he
runs out breaks runs out so now it's 98
and then I I broke and ran a really good
rack there in the end I was nervous as
hell but uh I pulled it out and uh made
some good shots yeah we were watching
that I mean it seemed like you got a
little off position a couple times but
you came right back stayed calm and uh
and played fantastic that wck what's
going through your mind when you're
running out and and you're maybe a
little bit not perfect the balls are a
little funny what what do you focus on
at that point uh I think most in that
moment it's more like get your body try
to get your body under control you know
because it's a big moment and I don't
play all the tournaments anymore so uh
you know I was like 10 weeks off after
the US Open just played the pro Star Cup
that was it and the rest uh you know
just making videos and like I consider
myself Semi-Pro now not full Pro anymore
cuz I want to I choose to stay more with
the family at home I want to see the
kids I don't want to be on the road 250
days a year and then have two kids you
know what is that for so you know
sometimes it takes a little while to get
used to the pressure again at the big
tournaments it's not it doesn't feel
like my living room anymore like when I
was in my 20s and 30s so yeah when it's
uh like that like 98 it's get your body
under control breathe well uh uh don't
take anything for granted just try to
keep it simple you know I've been there
before so it's just executing the shots
and try to let your body just do what it
knows how to do and don't don't fall
apart
that's all right last question uh you're
in top eight now what's your mindset
going forward is just one match at a
time or yeah just one match at a time
you know uh in this field I'm not going
to say like you know I haven't won a
major in in a long time so uh like if
you would be asking Fedor you might say
let's snap off another one but uh my
goal is just uh to get through this day
you know then would be another
semi-final at a major back to back so
that would be really good I mean final
eight I'm really happy with that already
but let's take take it a step further
you know I did semi's last one let's see
if we can uh go a little further now all
right also you want to give a shout out
so I know you do a lot of lessons I know
we follow you a lot obviously on the
shark stream uh you want to give a shout
where they get your lessons or anything
they want to get from you yeah I mean uh
I have the YouTube channel right new
Terminator fire a lot of people know
that and now of course I have the
Terminator College with the mental Edge
for competitive pool players course
that's uh you got to stay put because
from Monday that's going on sale for
Black Friday week that's 30% off so if
you want to work a little on the mental
part of the game which is everything you
know at at at our sport uh it's very uh
underestimated uh and I think it's the
missing link so go check that out and if
people have questions to shoot me a DM
on the socials and uh thank you very
much awesome thank you very much
appreciate Neil